{
    "riddles": [
      {
        "question": "What has keys but can't open locks?",
        "answer": "Piano"
      },
      {
        "question": "What has a head, a tail, but no body?",
        "answer": "Coin"
      },
      {
        "question": "I speak without a mouth and hear without ears. I have nobody, but I come alive with wind. What am I?",
        "answer": "Echo"
      },
      {
        "question": " I can cry without eyes and fly without wings. What am I?",
        "answer": "Cloud"
      },
      {
        "question": "I'm tall when I'm new and short when I'm old. What am I?",
        "answer": "Candle"
      },
      {
        "question": "What can fill a room but takes up no space?",
        "answer": "Light"
      },
      {
        "question": "What can you break without touching it?",
        "answer": "A promise"
      },
      {
        "question": "It belongs to you, but your friends use it more. What is it?",
        "answer": "Your name"
      },
      {
        "question": "I weigh almost nothing, but even the world's strongest man couldn't hold me for much longer than a minute or two. What am I?",
        "answer": "Breath"
      },
      {
        "question": " I can be bitter or sweet, but I'm always a treat, and in a bar or a cake, I'm something to eat. What am I?",
        "answer": "Chocolate"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am always in front and never behind. What am I?",
        "answer": "The future"
      },
      {
        "question": "If you have me, you will want to share me. If you share me, you will no longer have me. What am I?",
        "answer": "A secret"
      },
      {
        "question": "If you feed it, it lives; If you water it, it dies",
        "answer": "Fire"
      },
      {
        "question": "What begins and ends with an ‘e’ but only contains one letter?",
        "answer": "Envelope"
      }
    ]
  }
